Jai Hind.  The last day of ICICI Pro AMC has
arrived.  Brothers, people are asking whether I should apply or
not?  Because one of the biggest facts is that
three stocks of ICICI Bank were listed.
ICICI Group's I Should and none of them had
given positive listing.  Will he be able to
break this jinx this time or not
?
Hi everyone my name is your Vashane I am a
SEBI registered research analyst let's do it quickly
in 5 minutes that Bhaiya
what is going to be our final word of ICICI proc, do we have to
apply in full force, this is such a
big group, this is such a big IPO brand
value or do we have to apply in one or two lots,
how will we get share holder quota
without wasting time, let's deep
drive into our analysis but yes before
moving ahead if you have
not subscribed to the channel yet or are a new user
then you will get all the videos here.
I have posted here what mutual funds bought and sold in November.
Detailed analysis by Varun Berezes.
I have already posted the detailed analysis of ICICI Pidential AMC.
I have explained here how to get the share holder cat and how not to get it.
Today also we will
discuss it for a minute or two.  See
what subscription has been made so far in ICICI?  Let me
talk about that first.  Here we talk about QIB, it has happened
three times.
Talking about HAI category, it became 3.36 times.  If the
retail category reaches 0.83, then
most likely it will also be oversubscribed by tomorrow.
Shareholder
Kotak category also increased to 2.85 times and it has
already become 2x.  Look, the good thing is
that they don't have a deputy.
Most of the profit margins are
good for AMCs etc.
Everything has been explained in the main video.  Can
RBCO, HDFC, AMC, Aitya Birla,
all these have been explained in detail.
Now let us come to the final verdict
and let me
guide you a little more about the shareholder quota for 1-2 minutes.
Like every time, I will definitely
post the final word on Twitter and Telegram
that brother, what is going on with SME
IPOs, especially like you can see here,
Wake Fit Seems a Risky Bet with Low
Subscription, Avoid Rather than Taking a
Risk for 5 to 7% Gains, Corona Remedies,
brother, gains of around 10 to 20% will be made, you
can also apply for long term, SME
IPO Products, Avoid Riddhi Display,
Avoid Better to Avoid KV 3 to 40%,
I said it here and
four out of five analyses were done exactly dot to dot.
Look at this Wakefeed listed absolutely flat.
Kvitoy beans occurred in 33%.
Production went up just 4%.  Riddhi
display went to minus 20%.  Whereas the entire
IPO was oversubscribed.  Corona
Remedies I was expecting brother it will become 10 20
25%.  Massive went to 38% gains and
I also got it in the HAI category.
Twitter, Telegram community is absolutely free.  There are
no charges.  You will
find the link in the description pin comment.
If you are not following there yet, then
follow it.  See number one,
in which all can a person who does not have share holder quota apply?  Either he can do it
in retail and he can
apply to SHAI NI or BHAI etc.
Now who will get the shareholder quota
?  If
you had bought ICICI Bank shares on 4th December before 4th September, then it is still
valid.  If it is valid then
where can it be found?  Either he
can invest in the share holder quota category or
he can invest here in retail plus SH
or he can invest here in HAI
plus shareholder, now what does HAI mean,
whether you take small HAI or big
HAI plus share holder, someone was
asking whether I can invest in retail plus HNI
category, the answer is no, it will
not be invested together in retail HNI, it
is valid for those who have shareholder
quota, it is valid for everyone.  So those who have
shareholder quota have the benefit of two applications.
Coming to the final verdict.
Oversubscribed listing gains long term.
See, as I told you, you can keep these types of
companies for the long term
because the profit margins are good.
SIP is running on Book Day and Lifetime High Pay.  You
can keep it for the long term.
In that video also, we said in the main that there will be
over subscription around 3 to 5x.  2x already done.
Probably this
should cross 5x.  We have one day
left.  Look at the listing gains,
in that video also we had said that the listing gains will be around 5 to 10%.  The
final
verdict is still the same.  Listing gains will be around 5 to 10%.  If you are a
safe trader then you can
apply here in one or two lots.
If you had share holder
quota then invest one lot in retail and
half lot in share holder quota category.
If you can take a little risk, then
you can increase the number of lots or you
can invest from family accounts, friend
's account, family account etc.
so that our chances of allotment
increase here, but do not expect bumper gains
because the entire OFS is an IPO of Rs 10 crore, it is a
very big IPO and it is being
brought at high valuations, at a
price to book value of 30, hence, keep a little
listing and expect etc., so we are going to
invest in limited quantity,
friends, so this was the
final verdict of ICIC Pro AMC in which I am going to invest one or two lots,
one or two lots, but from different
multiple accounts.  If you like the video,
share it with your friends.  And yes, as I
told you about Twitter Telegram community,
which is absolutely free and there are
no charges.  The link is in the description pin comment.
Thank you for watching the video.  Lots
of love.  [Music]
[Music]